Rizky lan Indiarto

Malang, Indonesia, 65144 | +62-851-569-379-59 | rizkyian78@gmail.com | Indonesian

About Me

I am a Software Engineer, and Digital Nomad who has freelanced and worked full-time at startups to grow their platform businesses.

A believer that high-quality code and high-impact work can be done anywhere in the world, I have been working remotely from Asia for the past 2 years. While working remotely, I have created project that i most proud of Integrate with payment Allobank when opening of allobank festival who invited RED VELVET and NCT Dream and mostly indonesian fans is consider high, and able to complete it flawlessly.

Lastly, I am multilingual (English, Japanese, Indonesian) and able to collaborate with diverse teams to create global products.

Work Experience

System Developer (Payment Gateway)

Sep 2021 - Present

Brankas Pte Ltd

Remote

- Integrating Payment gateway with many payment method, for instance LinkAja, OVO, allopay, Visa, Master Card, and etc
- Planned development with team how to integrate payment and implement new feature of Brankas PG
- Troubleshooting error and bug when happened in production environment after release
- Successfully handled humongous transaction when "Allobank Festival" conducted by Bank Megas. The festival invited 2 distinguished Korean group band RED VELVET, and NCT Dream as in Indonesian fans is huge. We able to complete it flawlessly with processed 800 million IDR in single day
- Implemented SNAP (Indonesian Open API Payment Standard)

Part-Time Software Engineer

Jul 2020 - Present

PT. Nusantara Teknologi.

Jakarta, Indonesia

- Collaborated in application development by utilizing Typescript, NodeJS and Express as a backend framework, AWS as a cloud service provider, and MySQL
- Act as Full Stack Engineer engineering level for sustainable IT solution company with various achievement in forms of projects and products. Project that i handled
 - Siprus (Gov-owned Real Estate)
 - Pertamina VMI (Gov-owned Oil and Gas Company)
 - System Management Hotel
 - Telkom Neucentrix (Gov-owned telecommunication company)

Industrial Engineer

Jan 2021 - Jul 2022

GLINTS

Remote

- Mock Technical Interveiw: Conduct a Basic Javascript assessment for Final Period Glints Academy Student and giving them some advice.
- Participating in Hackathon conducted by GLINTS

Marketing Staff

Grand Ashoka

Sep 2016 - Jul 2019

Indonesia

Marketing through digital and traditional strategy in Malang Region

Education

Binar Academy Bootcamp Backend Engineering

Feb 2020 - May 2020 Remote

Brawijaya University
Bachelor Degree - Political Science

Sep 2013 - Dec 2018 Malang, Indonesia

Skills

Programming: Python, JavaScript, No-SQL, SQL, Swift, Node.js, Go, TypeScript, Kubernetes, Microservices, RabbitMQ, gRPC, GraphQL, Automation, SDLC, Docker, React, Flutter, Jenkins, CI/CD

Platforms: Linux (Ubuntu), Mac OS, Windows Software: X Code, Docker GUI, Visual Studio Code

Professional Organizations: Dev-C Malang, GoJakarta (Golang)

Communication: Public Speaking, Negotiation ,presentations (large and small audiences)

Languages: Bahasa (Native), English (Professional), Japanese (Conversational), Dutch (beginner)

Relevant Course

• SwiftUI & IOS Engineer: The Complete App Development Bootcamp

- Automating Infrastructure on Google Cloud with Terraform
- Integrate with Machine Learning APIs
- Serverless Firebase Development
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Masterclass
- React JavaScript
- React Native: Advanced Concepts
- Golang Fundamentals